yo yo this work for some people
check check my Twitter their work I'm
feeling it didn't go through Twitter no
comma but your RAF ship o'clock yeah
welcome welcome welcome
oh it's working right this is exciting
man I'm off periscope you all know I
love periscope is is the quality guy
because sometimes I go he's got good
let's see you know check the quality I
think I'm on Wi-Fi with my phone yo
check out all these giraffes y'all look
at him sahand a variant so guys we have
a we have a confession to make
oh yeah we have a little confession to
make there was a bug in the Honda
giraffes um on certain uncertain Havas
there was also an indicator light that
was staying on in the Civic so we have
fixed all the bugs um the three people
who already received Honda giraffes will
be receiving three replacements no need
to send the ones that you got back feel
free to do whatever you want with them
they are yours but you will also be
getting a brand new edition Honda
giraffe the latest and greatest in
giraffe quality oh you know I really do
like to stay in the other products dude
I wouldn't ship this stuff I don't think
it was good so that's why there was a
bit of a delay in shipping
but yeah so that's why there's a bit of
delay in shipping we want to make sure
that everything is really good before we
send it out so yeah we caught that in
testing we have extensive test plans for
all of our stuff we'll be pushing the
new yes so yeah kind of bugs I mean look
if it's working for you it's not like
it's some like bug that's gonna appear
we just forgot to connect some things so
we'll be pushing the new schematics to
to github giraffes are 100% Hardware
open-source I would love for the Chinese
to come and build knockoff giraffes and
sell them to rid of me because making
giraffes was a huge hassle but we did it
we did it we did it and here they are
they are all ready to ship we test each
giraffe individually the silicon them
yeah you'll be if you got one already
you'll be getting a new one even if you
haven't seen anything wrong oh I guess
you built one yeah it's it's just we
didn't we forgot to connect the
indicator line it's a stupid little
thing but you know we really like to
make sure everything's perfect before
you ship them because giraffes are gonna
be around for a while you know they're
they're not just for pandas but they
also have this port which will connect
to Neos or potentially new special
purpose hardware for driving cars but
obviously if you want to connect this
through your Eon panda to an eon giraffe
I said the name of the thing you know
the family guy the movie yeah that's
great okay do you have anything to show
off you know what each of the
combination of switches does for your
giraffe and that'll be shipping with
them today yeah this is the and Eddie's
gonna cut them himself for you yeah
we're gonna cut them with with a nice
paper cutter straight and we'll push it
to the go push this to the github also
so
you know no more questions about what
all the switches do hopefully as we like
to you know make things that are quality
and explain things rather than answer
support questions that's true we don't
like answering questions I'm subtle oh
you know what I do like overpriced
hoodies man look at the symphysis it's
embroidered men 129 dollars you can
dress like a comma a I employee and you
can just ships now hoodies ship now a
wheel get in hoodies in stock get in on
hoodies we're gonna change we're gonna
change both hoodies and giraffes to ship
within a week yeah giraffes pandas and
hoodies all ship immediately me I'm
waiting well Wednesday we ship on
Wednesday everyone says everyone's
everyone's days the shipping party yeah
yeah getting your hoodies tomorrow Yeah
right where do you get the hoodie shop
comma dot ai I'm shop that comment that
I buy hoodies Hale put put away it's
gonna be quick and fast if you order a
hoodie it is coming your way like within
the next week
we don't do turtlenecks do I look like
Steve Jobs we wear hoodies yeah 30 isn't
real nice jobs you know okay um welcome
thank you thank you all for watching
this periscope shop comm AI a buyer stop
I'm gonna update it right now
to say that the stuff is shipping right
away and updates on eons coming along
they're coming along we will definitely
meet the deadline as promised on the
website new sensor teaser no it's all
about the new said mission you know
about the new sensor no will it work on
a Picasso I think he's dead um yeah -
he's buy some overpriced hoodies man
they're great they really uh they're
nice and I like I said I stand behind
the product saltycomb AI we offer a
30-day
full money-back refunds if you send the
product back we buy it you don't like it
when your warranty on everything so if
anything breaks just send it back we'll
make sure to get you
we test the hoodies yeah we test the
hoodies they were pre worn not just
kidding just kidding they're new not
even made in sweatshops that's what the
box says um they're great hoodies free
hoodie rental no no nothing's free man
there's no such thing as a free lunch
put it this way if something's free look
for the small text oh I saw the new
Tesla's oh I really want a roadster man
like put it this way I was tempted to
buy a truck that's how much I wanted the
new Tesla's and then I split roadster
all right cool well you know the hoodie
the hoodie does not know promises they
might hey man the hoodie might inspire
you that's what hoodies do but giraffes
shipping out today and they'll ship out
really quick if you order I'm so yeah
shop.com may I check us out thanks for
watching